Washington and Lee University and Regional Virginia History Research Collection WLU.Coll.0668
Washington and Lee University, University Library Special Collections and Archives
- Biography, 1700-2018 (Box 2, Box 2-10)
  - Lewis, Sydney, 1999-03-13; Richmond Times-Dispatch (Box 6, Folder 26)
    File includes article by the Richmond Times-Dispatch.
    Lewis, Sydney
  - Link, O. Wilson (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Link, O. Winston (Ogle Winston)
  - Litzenburg, Thomas V. Jr. (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Litzenburg, Thomas V., Jr.
  - Logan, John Lee, 1890-02-20 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    File includes an obituary from the Lewiston Teller and an article In Memoriam by the Idaho Daily Statesman.
    Logan, John Lee, 1848-1890; Lewiston Teller; Idaho Daily Statesman
  - Lokale, Michael (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Lokale, Michael
  - Lord, Norman, 2000-10-04; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 6, Folder 31)
    File includes an obituary from The News-Gazette.
    Lord, Norman Franklin; Washington and Lee University, Department of Athletics, Track and Field
  - Lurate, Bob, 1991; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 6, Folder 32)
    File includes an article by the News-Gazette entitled "Shop to Feature Books, Items on War Era." In addition, the file includes a brochure to the Lexington Historical Shop and business card for Lurate.
    Lurate, Bob; Lexington Historical Shop
  - Lyle, John Blair, 1971; Virginia Cavalcade (Box 6, Folder 33)
    File includes an article from the Virginia Cavalcade entitled "John Blair and His 'Automatic Bookstore'."
    Virginia -- Lexington; Independent bookstores; Lyle, John Blair
  - MacCorkle, Daniel S., Washington and Lee University (Box 7, Folder 1)
    File includes three pages with information about MacCorkle for the Alumni Directory and Jacket File.
    MacCorkle, Daniel S., 1905-
  - MacCorkle, Stuart A., 1982; Washington and Lee University. News Office (Box 7, Folder 2)
    File includes a brief biography of MacCorkle by the Washington and Lee University News Office, a biographical statement, "Information for the Alumni Directory and Jacket File," and a picture of Stuart MacCorkle.
  - MacDonald, Ronald, 2008; Washington and Lee University, Department of Journalism and Mass Communications (Box 7, Folder 3)
    File includes two obituaries.
    MacDonald, Ronald Herbert
  - Magruder, George W. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Magruder, George W.
  - Manning, Dennis, 2001; The Roanoke Times (Box 7, Folder 5)
    File includes an article by the Roanoke Times entitled, "New Headmaster Mixes Work and Play."
    Manning, Dennis G.; Norfolk State University (Va.). Academy for Collegiate Excellence and Student Success
  - Mann, Larry (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Mann, Larry
  - Mann, Sally, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Mann, Sally
  - Matney, Angie (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Matney, Angela Renee
  - Matthews Family (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Matthews Family
  - Mattingly, Earl (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Mattingly, Earl Stansbury; Washington and Lee University. Treasurer; Washington and Lee University. Registrar
  - Maury, Matthew Fontaine (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Maury, Matthew Fontaine
  - McAleer, James (Box 7, Folder 12)
    McAleer, James
  - McCaig, Donald, 1991; Rural Living (Box 7, Folder 13)
    File includes a magazine article entitled, "Persisting in the Publishing World."
    McCaig, Donald
  - McClintock, J. William, 1994; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 7, Folder 14)
    File includes an obituary by the News Gazette.
    McClintock, J. William, 1931-1994
  - McCluer, John Parry, 1924; 2001; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.); Rockbridge County News (Box 7, Folder 15)
    File includes a 2001 article entitled, "The Man Behind the Name: New Biography Explores The Achievements of 'Fesser' McCluer" and obituaries for the Lexington Gazette and the Rockbridge County News.
    McCluer, Parry
  - McClung, Hunter (Box 7, Folder 16)
    File includes a photocopy of a short biography of McClung.
    McClung, Hunter, Dr.
  - McCormick, Cyrus Hall (Box 7, Folder 17)
    File includes a medal - Centennial of the Reaper, 1831-1931; a booklet entitled McCormick Celebration, September 25, 1931; a color brochure of the McCormick Farm; a biography from the McCormick International Harvester Collection Archives; and two copies of the Iron Worker featuring an article entitled, "Walnut Grove--Where Farm Mechanization Began."
    McCormick, Cyrus Hall, 1809-1884; McCormick Harvesting Machine Company
  - McCown, Albert Tardy, miscellaneous, 1947-1984; 17 Item (Box 7, Folder 18)
    File includes a program of retirement from 25 years of service to the Buena Vista City Public Schools, two biographies, and two photographs of Albert McCown, about 1955 and Oct. 1980. Also included an early color Christmas card printed by Albert, before his marriage, while he studied Industrial Arts at VPI. Also a Christmas card printed by Albert at his home in Kerrs Creek, Rockbridge County, VA, about 1970's, when he had his family, and an envelope of Albert's, McCown's Printing Service. Included is his name tag for the Virginia School Boards Association, Rockbridge County, with ribbons, Board Member, Delegate. A newspaper clipping, "McCown New Member of School Board," and photocopy of the News-Gazette clipping featuring Albert's service to the Rockbridge County School Board. Also included a return address envelope, Parry McCluer High School, Athletic Department, Buena Vista, VA 24416, maybe printed by Albert when he was Athletic Director there. A photo of Albert and coworker Industrial Arts Teacher, Ward Lockett.
    Also includes a 1969 issue of THE VISTA, which includes an article, "Teacher of the Month: Albert McCown." On the title page of this issue is a sketch of the Parry McCluer mascot.
    Included are a Father's Day card and Happy Birthday card, both made by his oldest daughter, Lisa. The Happy Birthday card is signed by Lisa, Josephine, his wife, and Jennifer, his youngest daughter.
    A Washington and Lee application for Admission, April 1, 1947, which was never turned in. Albert decided to go to VPI in Blacksburg, and graduated in 1957. He became the Industrial Arts Teacher at Parry McCluer High School in Buena Vista, Virginia, 1959-1984.
    McCown family; McCown, Albert T.; Washington and Lee University. Admissions Department; Parry McCluer High School; Rockbridge County, Virginia. School Board; Printing; Lockett, Ward
  - McCown, James L., Rockbridge County News; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.); The Dallas Daily Herald (Box 7, Folder 19)
    File includes a Rockbridge County News article entitled, "Civil War Memoirs of Mr. McCown Telling of Life in Northern Prison"; other brief newspaper notices about McCown from The Dallas Daily Herald; an obituary from the Lexington Gazette; and an image of Dr. Albert McCown and his father James L. McCown.
    McCown family; McCown, James L.; McCown, Albert T.
  - McCown, John, McCormick, Robert, 1780-1846 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    File includes a photocopy from the book, The McCormick Reaper Legend focusing on John McCown, the "Blade Maker."
    McCown, John
  - McCown, John Graham, 1934; The Roanoke Times (Box 7, Folder 21)
    File includes an obituary and picture of John Graham McCown.
    McCown, John Graham, 1918-1994
  - McCown, Josephine H., miscellaneous, 1952-2022; Marshall, Richard; 28 Item (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Invitation to Johnston-Willis Hospital School of Nursing graduation, May 16, 1952, including photocopy of photo as RN in 1952. Includes Miss Josephine Hotinger, R.N. pin worn at first job at the Stonewall Jackson Memorial Hospital. Whiteside Radio Service, Lexington, VA receipt to Josephine Hotinger for purchase of a TV set, etc..
    Includes Mrs. Josephine H. McCown, R.N. pin worn at the Stonewall Jackson Hospital, 1959-1971, along with hospital mask.
    Also includes miscellaneous documents, 1975, 1979, 2003 and 1970 American Red Cross Nursing Program card, and American Red Cross volunteer identification pin, worn while volunteering ath local bloodmobiles, after retiring in 1992. Also her American National Red Cross Nurse pin.
    File also includes photo of Josephine as W&L Student Health Head Nurse and W&L indentification pin worn as Head Nurse, biographical information written at her retirement from Washington and Lee University as head nurse of infirmary, 1992; as well as an article from the News-Gazette, entitled, "W&L Honors Employees At Banquet". Also included an ink pen, marked Josephine H. McCown, R.N., Head Nurse, Washington and Lee University.
    Included are two postcards from cousin Richard Marshall of Urbanna, Virginia, while in Paris, 1951, to Josephine, and the other to his grandmother, Susan Rader Hotinger (Mrs. Rice), 1952, while in Rome.
    Includes photo of Josephine as a little girl, ca.1930.
    Copy of Josephine's obituary from the News-Gazette, September 7, 2022. She passed away on August 31, 2022. Also included are her September 10 funeral service programs done by New Monmouth Church and Harrison's Funeral Home. Included is a letter of condolences from W&L President William C. Dudley, September 12, 2022.
    McCown, Josephine Hotinger; Stonewall Jackson Memorial Hospital; Stonewall Jackson Hospital; Washington and Lee University. Student Health Center
  - McCown Family Photos, 1909; 1939; 1991; 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    File includes 25 photographs and photocopies of photographs of the McCown family and their homes. Includes photographs of various generations and extended family members.
    Virginia -- Kerr's Creek; Virginia -- Staunton; Virginia -- Bath County; Virginia -- Healing Springs; McCown, Charles A.; McCown family; McCown, Alertie; McCown Boyts, Helen Siberia, 1908-1989; McCown, William Burnette, 1912-1982; McCown, Albert Orr; McCown, Albert T.; McCown, Josephine Hotinger; Mccown, Ruby Showalter; Showalter, W.L.; Lindsey Funeral Home; Showalter, Nannie; McCown, Margaret Virginia; Showalter, Howard; Silas, William; Charles, H. Bernard; McCown, Samuel Thompson; McCown, Ida Shelton; McCown, Mary Shelton; Mccown, Jennifer
  - McCown Family, 1908; 1909; 1919; 2002; 1989; 1982; 1937; 1918; The Coffeyville Daily Journal; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 7, Folder 24)
    File includes a wide range of materials. Various photocopies contain documentation of Charles A. McCown and Alertie C. Anderson's wedding in 1907. In addition, a list ascertains the burial of Charles A. McCown, Alertie McCown, and their infant at Fawn Creek Cemetary. A map of Montgomeny Co. KS. Cemeteries highlights cemetery 16 (Fawn Creek). Another map highlights the location of McCowan Springs in Bath County. Additionally, there are three articles by The Coffeyville Daily Journal. An article in The News-Gazette covers the recognition of Lisa McCown by the Rockbridge Historical Society in 2002. Finally, a small envelope contains a letter from Charles A. McCown to his mother Ida McCown, two wedding inviations from McCown weddings, memoriams from William B. McCown's passing, and a pamphlet made in memory of Helen McCown Boyts.
    Kansas -- Montgomery County; Kansas -- Coffeyville; Virginia -- Bath County; McCown, Charles A.; McCown, Alertie; The Coffeyville Daily Journal; McCown, Samuel Thompson; Rockbridge Historical Society; McCown, William Burnette, 1912-1982; McCown, Ida Shelton; McCown, Albert Orr; McCown Boyts, Helen Siberia, 1908-1989; Mccown, Ruby Showalter
  - McCown, William, 1872 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    File includes one letter from John W. McCoy to an unidentified person.
    McCoy, John W.
  - McCrory Family, 1835; 1838 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    File includes four items, two of which are letters between the McCrory siblings.
    McCrory, Julia A.; McCrory, Elizabeth; McCrory, Samuel H.
  - McCrum, Blanche, 1937; Columbia University; 1 Files (Box 7, Folder 27)
    File includes Columbia University's 1937 Report of the Dean of the School of Libary Service, which mentions of Blanche P. McCrum's tenure at the school.
    McCrum, Blanche Prichard
  - McCutchan, Frank, McCutchan, Frank, Rev.; 8 Item (Box 7, Folder 28)
    photocopies
    Rev. McCutchan, Biography, Glade Spring Presbyterian Church. A paper, "The Rank and Importance of Liberal Education," submitted by him, April 20, 1870, Washington College. A sermon by him in Waynesboro, September 14, 1879 and five sermons by him in Rogersville, Tennessee, transcripts, 1892, 1903, 1909, 1914-1915. Rev. Frank McCutchan
  - McDaniel, John, 2005; 1985-1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Fly fishing; McDaniel, John M., III (John Milton); Outdoor Sportsman Group. Fly Fisherman
  - McDowell, Daniel Henry, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    McDowell, David Henry
  - McDowell, Ephriam, John, and Samuel (Box 7, Folder 31)
    McDowell, Ephriam, 1672-1775; McDowell, Samuel, 1735-1817; McDowell, John, 1706-1742
  - McFarland, Francis (Box 7, Folder 32)
    McFarland, Francis W., Reverend
  - McKee, John (Box 7, Folder 33)
    McKee, William; McKee, John
  - McLaughlin, William (Box 7, Folder 34)
    McLaughlin, William
  - McLeod, Josephine, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    McLeod, Josephine
  - Menkemeller, Charles Allison (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Menkemeller, Charles Allison
  - Miles, A. Stevens, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Washington and Lee University. Omicron Delta Kappa; Miles, A. Stevens, Jr
  - Miley, Herbert (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Miley, Herbert
  - Miley, Michael (Box 7, Folder 39)
    Miley, Michael
  - Miller, James T. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Miller, James T., 1856-1927
  - Miller, James F., 1927 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Miller, James F.
  - Miller, Levi (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Miller, Levi
  - Miller, Louis F. "Weenie" (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Miller, Louis Franklin
  - Miriello, Frank (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Miriello, Frank A.
  - Mollenhoff, Clark (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Mollenhoff, Clark Raymond
  - Moore, David E. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Moore, David E.
  - Moore, Edward A. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Moore, Edward A.
  - Moore, James (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Moore, James
  - Moore, John Lyle (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Moore, John Lyle
  - Moore, John Preston (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Moore, John Preston
  - Moore, Thomas Harold (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Moore, Thomas Harold
  - Morrison, James (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Morrison, James, 1726-1804
  - Morrison, Robert Hall (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Morrison, Robert Hall
  - Morrison, William, 2010-04-14; 12 Item (Box 8, Folder 15)
    W&L History Class Brings Alum's Story to the Web, William Morrison started first modern human rights movement
    Morrison, William McCutchan, Reverend; Human Rights
  - Mudd, Roger (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Mudd, Roger
  - Murray, Albert (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Murray, Albert
  - Murray, Charles F. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Murray, Charles Fletcher
  - Neel, C.F. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Neel, Cyrus F.
  - Nelson, Robert William (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Nelson, Robert William
  - Newcomb Family (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Newcomb Family
  - Newton, Hope Hull (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Newton, Hope Hull
  - Northen, Mary Moody (Box 8, Folder 23)
    A Texas-Sized Donation for Virginia Colleges, by Gregory Turley, Washington and Lee Class of 1987.
    Northen, Mary Moody
  - Nuckols, Richard Henry (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Nuckols, Richard Henry
  - Nunnley, Lenora, 2009; 2 Item (Box 8, Folder 25)
    "This," World Catalyst Magazine, May 2009 and "Blue Lights," The Shine Journal, both by student Lenora Nunnley, WLU 2009
  - Osteen, John (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Osteen, John
  - Owen, Robert Latham (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Owen, Robert Latham
  - Padgett, Frank (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Padgett, Frank, ?-1854
  - Parker, Frank R. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Parker, Severn E. (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Parker, Severn Eyre
  - Patterson, Brown Craig (Box 8, Folder 31)
    Patterson, Brown Craig
  - Patton, James, 2010; Glanville, Jim; Mays, Ryan; 1 Item (Box 8, Folder 32)
    William Beverley, James Patton, and the Settling of the Shenandoah Valley, Essex County Museum and Historical Society Bulletin, v.55, November 2010
    Beverley, William; Patton, James; Shenandoah Valley
  - Paxton, Elizabeth Alexander (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Paxton, Thomas (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Paxton, Thomas, 1722-1788
  - Peabody, George (Box 8, Folder 35)
    Peabody, George, 1795-1869
  - Pence, Gilbert Eugene, 2015; 1 Files (Box 8, Folder 36)
    Pence, Gilbert Eugene
  - Peniston, Robert (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Peniston, Robert C.
  - Perry, Marvin Banks, Jr. (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Perry, Marvin Banks, Jr.
  - Person, Junius Randolph (Box 8, Folder 39)
    Person, Junius Randolph
  - Pleasants, Alfred W. (Box 8, Folder 40)
    Pleasants, Alfred W.
  - Pleasants, Jackie (Box 8, Folder 41)
    Pleasants, Jackie
  - Powell, Ottie Cline (Box 8, Folder 42)
    Powell, Ottie Cline
  - Preston, John T.L. (Box 8, Folder 43)
    Preston, John Thomas Lewis
  - Pusey, William Webb III (Box 8, Folder 44)
    Pusey, William W., III (William Webb)
  - Quinn, Robert R. (Box 8, Folder 45)
    Quinn, Robert R.
  - Ravenhorst, Albertina (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Ravenhorst, Albertina
  - Rayder, Sam (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Rayder, Sam
  - Read, John (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Read, John
  - Rhinesmith, W.D. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Rhinesmith, W. Donald
  - Rice, W. Thomas (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Rice, W. Thomas
  - Riegel, O.W. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold)
  - Ritz, Wilfred Julius (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Ritz, Wilfred Julius
  - Robbins, Tom (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Robbins, Tom
  - Robertson, A. Willis (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Robertson, A. Willis (Absalom Willis)
  - Robinson, John (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Robinson, John
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Root, E.C. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Root, E.C.
  - Rouse Family (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Rouse Family
  - Ruffner Family (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Ruffner family
  - Ruffner, Henry (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Ruffner, Henry, Reverend
  - Ruffner, William Henry (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Ruffner, William Henry
  - Rutherford, Robert (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Rutherford, Robert
  - Sallings, John Peter (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Schlegel, Robert (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Schlegel, Robert
  - Sensabaugh, Deborah (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Sensabaugh, Deborah
  - Sewall, Samuel Edmund (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Sewall, Samuel Edmund
  - Shafer, Susan (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Shafer, Susan
  - Shannon, Edgar (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Shannon, Edgar Finley, Jr., Dr.
  - Shannon, Samuel (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Shannon, Samuel
  - Shields, Jefferson (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Shields, Jefferson
  - Silver, Arthur (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Silver, Arthur
  - Smith, Henry Louis (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Smith, Henry Louis
  - Smith, Livingston Waddell (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Smith, Livingston Waddell
  - Snyder, Louis Vernon (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Snyder, Louis Vernon
  - Sprunt, David (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Sprunt, David Worth
  - Stewart, Robert (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Stewart, Robert
  - Still, Andrew T., 1 Item (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Doctor Andrew Taylor Still, Virginia and North Carolina Ancestors From Revolutionary Times to 1836
    Still, Andrew Taylor Still; Osteopathy; Moore, James; Horses
  - Sugrue, Thomas J. (Box 9, Folder 33)
    Sugrue, Thomas J.
  - Swaim, Curran (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Swaim, Curran
  - Switzer, Frank C. (Box 9, Folder 35)
    Switzer, Frank C.
  - Tate, William M. (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Tate, William M.
  - Taylor, Charles Holt (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Taylor, Charles Holt
  - Taylor, William (Box 9, Folder 38)
    Taylor, William
  - Telford, Robert Lee (Box 9, Folder 39)
    Telford, Robert Lee
  - Thompson, William M. (Box 9, Folder 40)
    Thompson, William M., 1864-1955
  - Tilson, Warren Edward "Tex" (Box 9, Folder 41)
    Tilson, Warren Edward
  - Tracy, Betty (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Tracy, Betty (Elizabeth Kilbourne), 1908-1993
  - Tucker, Robert H. (Box 9, Folder 43)
    Tucker, Robert Henry
  - Turnbull, Walter Jonathan (Box 9, Folder 44)
    Turnbull, Walter Jonathan
  - Turner, Charles (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Turner, Charles W. (Charles Wilson)
  - Tutwiler, Carrington C. (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Twombly, Cy (Box 9, Folder 47)
    Twombly, Cy
  - Valentine, Edward V. (Box 9, Folder 48)
    Valentine, Edward Virginius
  - Vethake, Henry (Box 9, Folder 49)
    Vethake, Henry
  - Wade, Wada (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Wade, Wada Phyllis
  - Walker, Forrest (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Walker, Forrest Edward
  - Warren, Mame (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Warren, Mame (Mary Elizabeth)
  - Washburn, William (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Washburn, William Crane
  - Washington, Booker T. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Washington, Booker T., 1856-1915
  - Washington, George (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Washington, George
  - Washington Family (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Washington Family
  - Watkin, Lawrence Edward (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Watkin, Lawrence Edward
  - Watkins, Richard (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Watkins, Richard
  - Watt, William (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Watt, William Joseph
  - Weaver, William (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Weaver, William
  - Webster Family (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Webster Family
  - White, Annie Jo (Box 10, Folder 13)
    White, Annie Jo
  - White, Archibald S. Jr (Box 10, Folder 14)
    White, Archibald S., Jr
  - White, B.D. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    White, B.D.
  - White, Henry Alexander (Box 10, Folder 16)
    White, Henry Alexander
  - White, James Jones (Box 10, Folder 17)
    White, James J. (James Jones)
  - Whitney, George (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Whitney, George S. (George Stephen)
  - Williams, Bob (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Williams, Bob
  - Williams, Boyd H. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Williams, Boyd H.
  - Williams, Charles W. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Williams, Charles Wiley
  - Williamson, Thomas Hoomes (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Williamson, Thomas Hoomes
  - Willis, Henry Parker (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Willis, Henry Parker
  - Wilson, John (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Wilson, John Delane
  - Wilson, William Lyne (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Wilson, William Lyne
  - Winchester, James R. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Biography: Winston, Daniel, 1950; 1 Item (Box 10, Folder 27)
    Daniel Winston, Former Slave, Buena Vista Resident, Marks Century of Life, Still Active. Roanoke Times
    Winston, Daniel; African Americans. Rockbridge County, Virginia
  - Wolfe, Thomas (Box 10, Folder 28)
    Wolfe, Thomas
  - Woods, Madalene and Michael (Box 10, Folder 29)
    Woods, Magdalene; Woods, Michael
  - Wu, Nelson i. (Box 10, Folder 30)
    Wu, Nelson I.
  - Young, Cy (Box 10, Folder 31)
    Young, Cy
  - Ziegler, Tom (Box 10, Folder 32)
    Ziegler, Thomas Joseph
  - Zimmer, Anne Carter (Box 10, Folder 33)
    Zimmer, Anne Carter
- Birds: Rockbridge, Co., VA (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Birds
- Books: Hardesty's (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Bridges (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
  - Bridges (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Bridges
  - Glenwood (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Brownsburg, Virginia, 1931-1939 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Folder includes newspaper article entitled, "Life of Blacks in Brownsburg Recalled", "Brownsburg of Old Recalled" and the "The Brownsburg Homicide". Also included is a pamphlet titles "Commencement Exercises Invitations for the Senior Class" (1933), in which students Everette Sensabaugh, Beatrice Hart, Mary Buchanan, Virginia Craig, Mary Lotts, Nellie Wade, Mary Ellen Sweet, Mitchell Swisher, and Hugh Adams are mentioned.The folder also conatins a copy of the "Historic Brownsburg Newsletter", volume 6, issue 1, March-April 2009.
  Virginia -- Brownsburg; Historic Brownsburg Newsletter; Brownsburg High School; Bare, Virginia R.; Wade, Herman J.; Sensabaugh, Thomas Everett; Sensabaugh, Dorothy; Bare, Emily Lorena; Patterson, Ed; Miller, Henry; African Americans. Brownsburg, Virginia.
- Buena Vista, Virginia (Box 11, Folder 6-9)
  Virginia -- Buena Vista
  - Buena Vista, Virginia (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Drawings (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Fire Department (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Virginia -- Buena Vista; Fire departments
  - Library (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Libraries; Virginia -- Buena Vista
- Buffalo Forge (Box 11, Folder 10)